find-name-meaning.com 2018-03-22

# Find Name Meaning

## Find Name Meaning - Privacy Policy

The text below shows Privacy Policy for the Apps that you use on Find Name Meaning. This privacy policy sets out how Find Name Meaning uses and protects any information that you give for Find Name Meaning Applications when you use them. Find Name Meaning is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When we ask you to provide certain information while authenticating the app and issuing certain permission by which you can be identified while using Applications, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Find Name Meaning may change this policy from time to time by updating this section. This privacy policy was last updated on 2nd June 2013. If we make any material changes to our policies, then we will either put message on our website or you need to check this section in order to comply with our policies. 

#### _What Data we collect?_

We **may** collect the following data from your profile:

  * We are collecting your basic profile information mainly your facebook profile photo, name, country, location.

#### _What we do with the Data we collected?_

We require this data to understand your needs and provide you with a good experience while using our Apps, and in particular way for the reasons below:

  * We use your basic informations to create funny photos which can be download! 
  * We require your certain information for the application you use to work

#### _How do we protect your information?_

We ensures at it best to keep your information secure. The use of this information is done while processing or using this Apps and which is temporary. 

  * We never get any sensitive details such as passwords.
  * We never store any details of facebook users.

#### _Do we disclose any information to outside parties?_

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. None of your informations are stored in our database.   
Find Name Meaning will not be responsible for any illegal activities on facebook. We never upload any data to facebook. By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

#### _3rd Party Advertisements and their Cookies:_

Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Third Party companies have their own Privacy Policies, Click to see company privacy policies:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting link below. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the link below. 

  * <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

#### _Contact:_

If you have any questions regarding privacy policy or queries please contact us via email at admin@Find Name Meaning.com

##### **Last Updated: 2nd Feb 2015**
